TJ! What's up? This place is incredible,
man. Thank you, man. I appreciate that.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
90 million, 100 million.
Growing up, did you think creating
all this was possible? I mean,
you got every car anybody can imagine.
You got the Ferrari out here, the Lamborghini,
the McLaren tucked in there.
I never had a broke mindset,
even when I was on government tees, even when
we had food stamps, even all of that stuff.
And then I built my business and
I've gone bankrupt. But it's been a long,
long, long time since I've been
broke and I ain't never going back.
Hey, never going back. I ain't never going back.
If you lost everything tomorrow,
could you make it all back?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
What business would you get into right now?
I started buying businesses. I mean, that's what
I would do because most people want to
build a business from scratch, but
you don't have to do that today.
You go get the playbook. You go get the playbook.
It's already done.
Do you believe in God?
Absolutely. I believe in God. Yeah, for sure. I
could tell you a story about that, but yeah,
absolutely.
A story. Has being in
LA helped you as an entrepreneur?
Absolutely. Come here.
This is amazing. I got to get
a video of this. This is not real.
That house right there, Kanye just moved into.
And the white one right there?
Yeah.
Did you go to college?
Did college help you become a millionaire?
No.
You made more than 99.9% of business professors
ever will. What's a lesson about business you'd
give to somebody that they
will not learn at business school?
Guys, I'm out in the hidden hills in Beverly
Hills out in Los Angeles, and I'm about to
interview a $100 million entrepreneur who built and
sold a tech company at his $50 million mansion
out here, you guys. This is about to be
a masterclass on all things business to figure out
how now he owns a business.
He owns 10 companies doing over $100 million
a year and really figuring out the secrets
to success and building wealth and how
you can become financially free headed into 2025.
So let's go meet up with him
and go see what he has to say.
TJ.
What's up?
What's going on, my friend?
Good to see you, bro.
Thank you for having us out here.
For sure.
This place is incredible, man.
Thank you, man. I appreciate that.
Man, how long has Beverly Hills been home for?
Beverly Hills, about four years.
And you built an empire.
Yeah, man.
How long have you been a business owner for?
Man, most of my life.
Most of your life?
Most of your life.
Yeah, for sure.
Is there anything that you've
built that has become impossible?
I mean, you got every car anybody can imagine.
You've got the Ferrari out here,
the Lamborghini, the McLaren tucked in there.
Yeah.
Well, I've always loved cars, man.
So I've always thought that I
would have cars that I wanted.
So I didn't know that it would be these.
But yeah.
What was your main business?
Tech.
Tech Services.
I built a tech services business, sold it.
And then I built a construction business.
Sold it.
And I have a supplement business today.
I built businesses, man.
I hope other people do the same thing.
How many businesses would you say you own right now?
About...
Just under 10.
But, yeah.
the way out here from austin yeah and we got to
get the game from you man we got to figure out
like how people can become wealthy going into 2025
okay going into the new year and they want
to take over and dominate like you did in multiple
industries can we get some game for you real quick
for sure let's get right into it throughout your
career across all your companies in one year in
terms of revenue what was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year across my companies
in revenue oh wow 90 90 million 100
million actually and how about for yourself 25 million
yeah yeah that's incredible yeah do you come from
a lot of money absolutely not man no absolutely
so you didn't have rich parents no not at all
my mom was 14 years old when she got pregnant with
me i grew up in the south food stamps
and government cheese and all that sort of stuff so
what was the turning point to financial freedom how
did you know you wanted to get really serious
about building a hundred million dollar
company and just becoming an extremely successful
entrepreneur you know i think when i was a
kid man i always wanted to be successful because i
didn't want to live in the stuff that i was living
in i didn't like it i was motivated to get out of
it so i didn't know that i wanted to be
successful i didn't know that i wanted to be successful
i didn't know that i wanted to be successful i didn't know that
i wanted to be successful i didn't know that i wanted to be successful
to build a hundred million dollar company per se but
what i did know is i wanted to be successful i
didn't know what that looked like and you continue to
define that as you grow but i wanted to be
successful early on so i always worked always tried
to figure a way out to be helpful and had
a mindset that was like oh how do i get out
of this place and never have to come back to it now
as an eight nine figure entrepreneur what was
the best financial advice that you ever received i
don't know that i got a lot of financial advice
i got business advice but in terms of finance advice
the advice that i would give your
followers is to learn and make money
you don't need to be a millionaire this
is everything that i tell people all the time
that you do you have to be a millionaire you
have to be successful at least get a lot of
money in your sleep right no matter what i
don't care if you're getting paid like don't trade
dollars for hours because no matter how much
you charge per hour you're going to be limited
so you have to figure out how to
make passive income and build systems invest do different
things that you're making more money while you sleep
than you can in any job so let's say
somebody is trading their time for money they're in
that nine to five they want to make that lead
to becoming financially free they want to
start making passive income what's that first step
somebody should take real estate is a good one you
have to have a lot of capital to start making money
have to have a lot of capital. There's a
lot of first-time homeowner programs. I think the biggest
thing that one would do today, if I was, because,
you know, what I did is different than what I would
do today. What would you do today? Today, what I
would do is I would buy businesses. You know, that is
the thing that I would do because right now,
there are so many businesses that are ripe for
selling. There are so many people that want to get
out of their business. Their kids don't want to go
into that business. They don't have maybe succession plans.
They don't have a way to get out of that
business, but they need the cash and they
need to stop because they've gotten divorced, they're sick,
they're tired, whatever it is. I would use
the government 7A program to get financing to buy
businesses. Is that SBA? SBA 7A program, yeah. What
type of business would you buy in today's world?
You can buy laundromats. The focus is getting
stuff that cash flows. So laundromat, pool companies. I
like the vending machine business. I like
laundromats. I like things like that because
it's not necessarily labor intensive or you have to
have a lot of know-how to do that. And they're
recession-proof. They're recession-proof, man. They're going
to always be there. So buying
businesses is what I would be
doing today. Like the private equity model?
Well, it's not so much private equity, right?
It's leveraged buyouts. So what you're doing is
you're finding businesses that cash flow at
a certain number. Let's say that business cash
flows at $20,000 a month, right? And you can get
a loan. You can service a loan for $7,000 a month
or $10,000 a month. You're up $10,000, right? So what
you want to do is to figure out a way to
creatively pay the person that wants to leave the
business and buy businesses. I mean, that'd be the
thing that I do. Have you ever been broke before?
Yeah, I've been broke before.
Broke in terms of no money, not broke
mindset, right? That's a whole different thing. I never
had a broke mindset, even when I was on government
tees, even when we had food stamps, even all of
that stuff. We had no money, but I
personally was never broke because I was always thinking
way beyond where I was, right? And then I built
my business and I've gone bankrupt. But it's been a
long, long, long time since I've been
broke and I ain't never going back.
Hey, never going back.
I ain't never going back.
I love that. I love that. So if you
lost everything tomorrow, could you make it all back?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
What business would you get into right now?
I started buying businesses. If I lost
everything tomorrow, I would start buying businesses. Why?
Because you're buying it based on the
other business's credit, right? There's all types of
creative financing to do. There's SBA loans, the 7A
SBA loans that I talked about. So yeah, I would
go do that. That would be the fastest. I
mean, that's what I would do because most people want
to build a business from scratch, but
you don't have to do that today.
You go get the playbook. You go get the playbook.
It's already done. The business is already
done. You can see that it's working.
Where do you go to find these
businesses? Some people hear that, they say, okay,
just buy a business, but where can you find
people? Where do you go to buy a business?
Yeah. I think there's a number of portals.
There's a biz by sell, I think it is,
but there's a portal that you can just
go in and put in the industry, the location,
and that kind of thing. And it brings up
all the businesses and people are trying to buy businesses
or trying to sell their businesses. There's
business brokers. And then you can also start
to just cold call businesses because there's
people that would sell their business if they
got the call, but they haven't gotten the
call. Big transfer of wealth is about to happen.
It's what you're saying. People are
looking to step out of their business.
Yeah. It's called the, I think it's called the
SBA. Yeah. It's called the SBA.
Yeah. It's called the SBA. Yeah. It's called the SBA.
It's called the SBA. Yeah. It's called the gray
tsunami. And the gray tsunami is there's a lot of
boomers that have businesses that they have to get
out of. There's a surplus of businesses and not
enough people that's going out and buying
businesses. But wouldn't they want to give
that to their family to take over?
There are a lot of family members,
man, that kids don't want to go do their
dad's business. They want to do their own thing. We're
in a different time. You guys, this video with TJ
has been incredible so far and we're about to get
right back to it. But I have a very quick,
very special announcement to make for you guys. So a
couple months ago, I launched and built
one of the biggest and greatest entrepreneur communities
in the entire world. And you can join
this community today for free. And inside of this
community, I bring in the biggest business owners
in the world, even billionaires, all the people
that you see me interview on live calls to
directly mentor you, where you can ask them any
question about business, starting and scaling a business,
how to sell, how to market, how to find
a winning product and scale that in whatever industry
that it is in. I want you guys to stop
for a second and think about something. Are you
a business owner? Are you a business owner? Are you
in the exact same place now that you were
a year ago or even the year before? Maybe you're
hesitating to start that first business or you
don't know how to scale that company that you
started. You don't know how to get out
of that nine to five. Understand this. Nothing changes
if nothing changes. If you're still taking advice from
the same people who are not even in the
places that you want to be, you need to stop
and get around people that have done it before. And
that's why I'm giving you guys the opportunity
today to join my community for free, to come
learn from the most successful and
the wealthiest business owners in the world,
because the only way to go from point A to
point B in life, in business, in your career and finances
is through mentorship. It's getting the lessons,
the blueprint, the playbook from the people that
have been there and done it before, regardless of
what industry you're in. So if you want to join
and come learn from the billionaires and
the multimillionaires that I interview, how to build
wealth and start becoming financially free, go to
the link down in the description of this video
to join the school of mentors. I can't wait
to see you on the inside. With that being said,
let's get back to the video. Do you believe
in God? Absolutely. I believe in God. Yeah, for sure.
I could tell you a story about that, but yeah,
absolutely. A story. So as a kid, I was broke,
didn't have a wonderful sort of environment. So
I was always like going, God, show me yourself.
Show me who you are. Show me your face,
right? Show me in the Magic Johnson poster, you know,
do something, right? And then I went to work
the next day. I remember going to sleep crying and
wondering if God is real or was he Santa
Claus. And I'm working, doing my thing. And this guy
comes up and says to me, God loves you. He's real.
And he wanted me to tell you that. And from that
moment on, I was 15 years
old. I've always believed in God.
God, you know, so. And faith has been
pretty important for you. Faith is important. I mean,
faith is critical. Faith is critical, obviously
from a spiritual standpoint, but from a business
standpoint and from a life standpoint, if you
don't believe it, like when you believe something,
truly, truly believe something, it's going to drive
your actions. It's going to drive the way
you think and what you do in the
relationships that you build. So faith is really important.
So God gives us a practical foundation for faith.
He said, believe. I mean, that's what the whole
New Testament is about. Did you go to
college? Yeah. Did college help you become a millionaire?
No. It didn't hurt me. I mean, what college did for
me is help me get a skill set. It helped me
become a computer programmer and get a job as
a computer programmer. So let me ask you this,
because you made more than 99.9% of
business professors ever will. What's a lesson about
business you'd give to somebody that they
will not learn in business school? Marketing. What
they don't teach in school is that everybody
needs you. They just don't know who you are.
So your job is to identify who
those people are, get to the highest mountain,
top that you can, and tell them who you are.
Let the people know who you are. That is the key
to growing in business. And in school, we learn
about business, but marketing is the key to making
it all come together. You have the magic sauce,
but if people don't know who you are, then it
doesn't matter. Now, we came all the way out here
from Austin. Can we check out the spot real quick?
See the place? Is that cool? Yeah, for sure.
Awesome, man. It's so cool.
Has being in LA helped you
as an entrepreneur? Absolutely. Come here.
This is amazing. This is amazing. I got to
get a video of this. This is not real.
If you come over here.
So this house, Mark Wahlberg's house.
He still lives there? No, he sold it about
seven, eight months ago. That house right up there,
trees are kind of covering it a bit.
The driveway goes all the way down there.
The tennis court is associated with that. And then
on the bottom of that, he has a car museum.
That's Samsung. The Samsung counter?
Yeah. Wow. That house right there, Kanye just moved into.
And the white one right there?
Yeah. That house, the gray one?
Yeah. That's Aston Kutcher's house.
Oh my goodness. They call it the farmhouse.
Denzel Washington, Eddie Murphy. Are you serious?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. They're all about here?
Yeah, yeah. That's wild. This is
all Beverly Park. So when you say,
has it helped me? One thing that happens is that
you can't unsee stuff. So like when I was in DC,
I love cars. And I would have a
few cars and I would have people going,
man, I love cars. And I would have people going,
man, be careful. Don't do that. Don't do that.
You can't do these things. And you come out here
and you like meet people and they have a 20
car garage and a 50 car car collection or a hundred
car car collection. So you find your tribe and
you see that things are possible. And once you
see that it's possible, you can't unsee it.
So has it helped me as an entrepreneur? Absolutely.
Because it just expands your vision and helps
your creativity. And you find out ways to do
things that you wouldn't even think was possible back home.
What's the number one thing that separates
middle class from wealthy people in today's world?
No limits.
I mean, wealthy people don't have a limitation and
they know there's no limit in terms of what
they can achieve and how much money they can
make. And all they have to do is solve problems,
create solutions to make more money. And so they
live in that world. And it's a whole different
realm where it's not about jobs and how much you
can make on this job or stepping up a particular
ladder around some stuff that's
sort of predetermined and well-structured. Wealthy
people don't need structure. Well, TJ, this
was absolutely amazing. I got to say,
thank you so much for having
us out here. Well, thanks for trespassing.
Good to see you, man. Well, I got to
ask you though. So this summer, I started a private
community called the School of Mentors. It's
grown to be one of the biggest entrepreneur
communities in the world. Awesome. Every single week
I host live calls with the millionaires and
the billionaires that I interview, such as
like the former CEO of 7-Eleven, Stephen Klubeck,
who sold his company for $2 billion to Hilton. I'd
love to have you on a live call. Could we
make that happen? Could you be a mentor on
a live call? Absolutely. That'd be amazing, my friend.
Everybody, if you guys want to join me,
please do. Thank you so much. Thank you.
Go to the link down in the description
of this video to join the School of Mentors,
to get mentored directly from the millionaires
and the billionaires I interview every single week.
TJ, where can everybody find you guys?
TJ Millionaire Mentor on Instagram, on YouTube.
And everybody go tap in with
TJ right now, like and subscribe,
and we'll see everybody in here on the next video.